Finding Aid for the Ruth Frey Axe Collection of Material about H.H. Bancroft and Company LSC.1427
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Xerox copies, 13 items
  - Schoolbooks, Item No. 105 (Box 5)
    - HRW to Library Education, UC, Item No. 105; 1 page (Box 5)
    - HRW to Miss Wilma W. Waite acknowledging her letter and list, August 15, l949; Item No. 105; 2 pages (Box 5)
    - Miss Wilma Waite letter and list of UC Ed library holdings, August 4, 1949; Item No. 105; 5 pages (Box 5)
    - HRW July 29 to Miss Waite, Item No. 105; 1 page (Box 5)
    - Miss Waite to HRW March 8 with list, Item No. 105; 2 pages (Box 5)
    - Letter HRW to Miss Waite, March 15, 1949; Item No. 105; 1 page (Box 5)
    - Letter of from Yale, June 6, 1949; Item No. 105; 1 page (Box 5)
    - Ack. HRW to Yale letter, Item No. 105; 1 page (Box 5)
    - Advertisement in Swett's Common School Readings, Item No. 105; 3 pages (Box 5)
    - California State Library Works by Charles Russell Clarke, Item No. 105; 1 page (Box 5)
    - Letter of William F. Kelleher, January 23, 1950; Item No. 105; 2 pages (Box 5)
      re holograph letter of Bancroft about publishing schoolbooks.
    - Original in this coll., Item No. 105 (Box 5)
      See Item No. 64.
    - "My notes", Item No. 105; yellow paper, 2 pages (Box 5)
    - Letter R. Axe to Reference Librarian, Nevada State Historical Society, October 29, 1972; Item No. 105; 1 page (Box 5)
    - Reply Has Warren's Intermediate Geog., November 1, 1972; Item No. 105; 1 page (Box 5)
    - Letter R. Axe to Nevada State Historical Society, 11-472, Item No. 105; 1 page (Box 5)
    - Letter R. Axe to Librarian, Oregon State Library one with his notes, May 27, 1977; Item No. 105; 2 pages (Box 5)
    - Bancroft schoolbook imprints, Item No. 105; 2 pages xerox (Box 5)
    - Letter R. Axe to Bancroft Library, May 13, 1971; Item No. 105; 1 page, yellow paper (Box 5)
    - R. Axe notes, Item No. 105; 2 pages (Box 5)
  - Book of the Fair
    - "My notes on UCLA copies", Item No. 106; 6 pages, plus 1 page (Box 5)
    - "My notes on Los Angeles Public Library copy", Item No. 106; 1 page (Box 5)
    - Letter of Mr. Lake, Riverside Public Library with description of their copy, November 1, 1948; Item No. 106; 1 page (Box 5)
    - "My chart" California Historical Society, UCLA, California State Library, Los Angeles Public, Riverside copies, Item No. 106; 1 page (Box 5)
    - Letter Ruth Axe to Silveira de Braganza and Jake Zeitlin, February 27, 1971; Item No. 106; 1 page (Box 5)
    - Letter HRW to Peter Decker send Book of Fair to CHS, December 27, 1949; Item No. 106; 1 page (Box 5)
    - Letter to Edna Parratt, December 27, 1949; Item No. 106; 1 page (Box 5)
    - Description of Book of Fair received at CHS, Item No. 106; 1 page (Box 5)
  - Book of Wealth or Achievements of Civilization
    - Chart of UCLA copies, Item No. 106; 1 page (Box 5)
    - HRW to Eleanor Bancroft question, August 17, 1948; Item No. 106; 1 page (Box 5)
    - Ralph Lyon to HRW, October 11, 1948; Item No. 106; 4 pages (Box 5)
    - HRW to Ralph Lyon, October 15, 1948; Item No. 106; 1 page (Box 5)
    - HRW to Ralph Lyon, October 19, 1949; Item No. 106; 1 page (Box 5)
    - HRW to Ralph Lyon, October 8, 1948; Item No. 106; 1 page (Box 5)
    - HRW to Ralph Lyon, December 1, 1948; Item No. 106; 1 page (Box 5)
    - Ralph Lyon to HRW, October 21, 1948; Item No. 106; 3 pages. (Box 5)
    - HRW to Ralph Lyon, October 28, 1949; Item No. 106; 1 page (Box 5)
    - HRW to Ralph Lyon, October 29, 1948; Item No. 106; 1 page (Box 5)
    - Ralph Lyon to HRW, November 8, 1948; Item No. 106; 2 pages. (Box 5)
    - HRW to Ralph Lyon, November 12, 1948; Item No. 106; 1 page (Box 5)
    - Mabel Gillie, California State Library, October 22, 1948; Item No. 106; 1 page (Box 5)
    - HRW to Miss California State Library, November 4, 1949; Item No. 106; 1 page (Box 5)
    - Miss Caroline Wenzel, California State Library, June 24, 1949; Item No. 106; 1 page (Box 5)
    - Description of California State Library Book of Wealth, Item No. 106; 2 pages (Box 5)
    - Letter Ralph Lyon to HRW, November 2, 1949; Item No. 106; 1 page (Box 5)
    - Letter HRW to Librarian Wesleyan, University Library, Middletown, Connecticut, October 27 1949; Item No. 106; 1 page (Box 5)
      - Reply of Librarian Wesleyan, University Library, Middletown, Connecticut, November 8, 1949; Item No. 106; 1 page (Box 5)
    - List of Subscriptions & amounts subscribed from Fullerton Special Collections (Stone papers), Item No. 106; 3 pages (Box 5)
    - Letter HRW to Mr. Lake (Riverside Public Library), October 25, 1948; Item No. 106 (Box 5)
    - Letter Mr. Lake To HRW, November 8, 1948; Item No. 106 (Box 5)
    - Card Mr. Lake to HRW, November 23, 1949; Item No. 106 (Box 5)
    - HRW to Miss Caroline Wenzel, California State Library, January 28, 1949; Item No. 106 (Box 5)
      - Card of Miss Wenzel, reply, Item No. 106 (Box 5)
    - "My Chart" - Frick collection, California State Library, Ban Author's and Fin de Siecle No name editions, Riverside, Item No. 106 (Box 5)
    - "My description" Riverside copy, Item No. 106; 1 page (Box 5)
    - Letter Franklin Biebel Frick Library, February 21, 1949; Item No. 106; 1 page (Box 5)
    - Description Frick copy Cogne Noir (NYPL has Cygne noir), Item No. 106; 2 pages. (Box 5)
    - Description, California State Library, Item No. 106; 1 page (Box 5)
    - Letter HRW to Frick, January 24, 1949; Item No. 106; 1 page (Box 5)
    - Letter HRW to Frick, February 7, 1949; Item No. 106; 1 page (Box 5)
    - Letter, Pierpont Morgan Library, Fred Adams to T.W. Streeter, No copy in, Item No. 106; 1 page (Box 5)
    - Frick to HRW, February 1, 1949; Item No. 106; 1 page (Box 5)
    - Wesleyan to HRW, November 1, 1949; Item No. 106; 1 page (Box 5)
    - NYPL to HRW, March 9, 1949; Item No. 106; 1 page (Box 5)
    - R. Axe to Riverside Public Library, February 11, 1949; Item No. 106; 1 page (Box 5)
    - HRW to Riverside Public Library, November 2, 1948; Item No. 106; 1 page (Box 5)
    - Description of Frick copy to Riverside, Item No. 106; 1 page (Box 5)
    - HRW to Ralph Lyon, March 1, 1949; Item No. 106; 1 page (Box 5)
    - Letter HRW to Director New York Historical Society re Book of Wealth, March 2, 1949; Item No. 106; 1 page (Box 5)
    - Letter HRW to Reference Librarian, NYPL, March 2, 1949; Item No. 106; 1 page (Box 5)
    - Letter Ralph Lyon re his holdings of Book of Wealth, March 7, 1949; Item No. 106; 1 page (Box 5)
    - Letter HRW to Ralph Lyon, thank you, March 11, 1949; Item No. 106; 1 page (Box 5)
    - Letter, Ralph Lyon will ask mother about A.L. Bancroft, October 29, 1948; Item No. 106; 2 pages (Box 5)
    - Questionnaire HRW to Ralph Lyons re the Bancrofts filled in and answered and returned, March 22, 1949; Item No. 106; 2 pages (Box 5)
    - Letter HRW to Librarian Wesleyan U, Item No. 106; 1 page (Box 5)
    - Pencil chart, UCLA Book of Wealth copies, Item No. 106; 1 page (Box 5)
    - California State Library copy of Book of Wealth some notes in HRW's writing, Item No. 106; 6 pages (Box 5)
    - Letter, HRW to Eleanor Bancroft, November 4, l949; Item No. 106; 1 page (Box 5)
    - Letter, HRW to Mr. Lake, Riverside Public Library, Item No. 106; 1 page (Box 5)
    - Letter, Andrew Horn to HRW, February 3, 1950; Item No. 106 (Box 5)
    - Letter, Andrew Horn to HRW, February 23, 1950; Item No. 106 (Box 5)
    - Letter, HRW to Andrew Horn, February 6, 1950; Item No. 106 (Box 5)
    - Letter, HRW to Andrew Horn, February 28, 1950; Item No. 106 (Box 5)
    - Letter, Ralph Lyon price of Book of Wealth, April 27, 1954; Item No. 106 (Box 5)
    - Letter, Ralph Lyon, April 7, 1954; Item No. 106 (Box 5)
    - "My notes on Riverside copy Book of Wealth", Item No. 106; 1 page, 2 sides (Box 5)
      - "1 side Henry Lebbeus Oak by ...Ora Oak, my notes", Item No. 106 (Box 5)
    - "My notes" Portfolios, Item No. 106; 1 page, newsprint (Box 5)
    - California State Library, List of Bancroft books including Book of Wealth, Item No. 106; 2 pages (Box 5)
  - The History Company Inc. forfeit, September 23, 1886 December 14, 1905; Item No. 107 (Box 5)
    - List of imprints and descriptions, Item No. 107; 24 pages (Box 5)
    - Additional notes, Item No. 107; 24 pages (Box 5)
    - Additions, Item No. 107; 8 pages (Box 5)
    - UCLA holdings descriptions filled in, Item No. 107; 2 pages (Box 5)
  - The Bancroft Co. Inc. Forfeit, June 22, 187? December 4, 1905; Item No. 108 (Box 5)
    - List of imprints and descriptions, locations, Item No. 108; 15 pages (Box 5)
    - To California State Library and Bancroft, Item No. 108; 2 pages (Box 5)
    - To UCLA, all filled in, Item No. 108; 3 pages (Box 5)
    - To Bancroft, filled in, Item No. 108; 2 pages (Box 5)
    - Letter, Hager to Historical Society of Montana, February 29, 1964; Item No. 108; 1 page (with copy) (Box 5)
    - University of Washington, Library Pacific Northwest collection letter to Hager, March 9, 1964; Item No. 108; 1 page (Box 5)
    - Bancroft Co. publications, Item No. 108; 1 page (4 copies) (Box 5)
    - Hager to Southwest Museum, February 29, 1964; Item No. 108; 1 page (Box 5)
    - Hager to Solano County Free Library, copy, March 2, 1964; Item No. 108; 1 page (Box 5)
    - John Barr Tompkins Bancroft Library to Hager, March 4, 1964; Item No. 108; 2 pages (Box 5)
    - California State Library to Hager, May 12, 1964; Item No. 108; 1 page (Box 5)
      with Bancroft Co. imprint list, 2 pages
  - List of W. B. Bancroft imprints (he was a newphew of H.H.), Item No. 109; 2 pages (Box 5)
    - Copy partial list of ephemera, Item No. 109; 2 pages (Box 5)
  - T. Percival Gerson Collection, Item No. 110 (Box 5)
    - Letter holograph to HRW inviting Ruth Axe to his house on March 25, 1950 to work on his collection, March 22, 1950; Item No. 110; 1 page (Box 5)
      "This was was long before he sold his collection to UCLA, and was his complete collection. The following and may not be my complete notes, however."
    - Notes, Item No. 110; 3 pages. (Box 5)
    - 1 paragraph on Knight's remarks about formation of Bancroft, Knight & Co., 1877-1878; Item No. 110; 1 page (Box 5)
    - Notes, Item No. 110; 1 ½ pages (Box 5)
    - Wrathful pioneers notes, September 17, 1951; Item No. 110; 4 pages (Box 5)
    - Article Los Angeles Times by William K. Knight on collaboration with Bancroft, March 10, 1918; Item No. 110; 8 pages (Box 5)
    - "My notes on letters of William H. Knight", Item No. 110; 2 pages (Box 5)
    - "My notes on Ambrose Bierce", (circa 1888); Item No. 110; 3 pages (Box 5)
    - "My notes", Item No. 110; 1 page (Box 5)
    - In Out West by Charles F. Lummis, December 26, 1925; Item No. 110; 2 pages (Box 5)
    - Asiatic Labor Urgently Needed reprint by Los Angeles Times article by K.H. Bancroft, May 24, 1907; Item No. 110; 3 pages. (Box 5)
    - "My notes", Item No. 110; 1 page (Box 5)
    - Letter of A.L. Bancroft & Co. assuring that publication will continue of Bancroft's work after the fire of April 30th, May, 7, 1886; Item No. 110; 1 page (Box 5)
    - Biographical index of Gerson collection at UCLA, Item No. 110; 29 p. mimeographed (Box 5)
  - Miscellaneous HHB, Item No. 111 (Box 5)
  - Material from Bancroft article and Introduction, Item No. 112 (Box 5)
    - HRW marked p. 2, Item No. 112; 1 page (Box 5)
    - HRW, Item No. 112; 1 page and ½ holograph (Box 5)
    - California newspapers in Roadblocking article, 1907 book, Item No. 112; 1 page (Box 5)
    - Doxsee quotes HRW, Item No. 112; 1 page, newsprint (Box 5)
    - From method chapter, Item No. 112; 1 page (Box 5)
    - H.H. Bancroft Co., Item No. 112; 4 pages, newsprint (Box 5)
    - Bancroft Progress, Item No. 112; pages 2 and 3 (Box 5)
    - III, Item No. 112; page 7 (Box 5)
    - End of Annals HHB, Item No. 112 (Box 5)
    - Portfolios, Item No. 112; 1 page (Box 5)
    - Plates in 1891 edition of Lit. Ind., Item No. 112; 1 page (Box 5)
    - The Bookseller, Item No. 112; 1 page (Box 5)
    - Oak's estimate of Bancroft's writings, Item No. 112; holograph; 1 page, both sides (Box 5)
    - Marked 2, Item No. 112; 1 page (Box 5)
    - Alleged Bancroft publication not yet located. HHB Many since found, June 1951; Item No. 112; 10 pages (Box 5)
    - ALB not yet located (many since found), Item No. 112; pages 3-9 (Box 5)
  - From Lyons's Book of the Fair, Item No. 113; 3 photostats (Box 5)
  - For Book of Fair (received from Warren Howell in 1972), Item No. 113; 2 ads (Box 5)
  - Catalogo de las obras publicadas en Español por The History Company ....History Building San Francisco, California, 1890; Item No. 114; 25 pages (Box 5)
  - Obras Historicasde Huberto Howe Bancroft, 1883; Item No. 115; 22 pages (Box 5)
  - From CSL Sargent Epes Standard First Reader xerox of one of the earliest HHB publications, only copy known, Item No. 116; 4 sheets and letter (Box 5)
  - Schoolbooks
    - Photograph letter (HHB) schoolbook publishing (org in coll), Item No. 118; 2 pages. (Box 5)
    - Pacific Coast Fourth Reader, Item No. 118; 8 sheets (Box 5)
    - Pacific Coast Fourth Reader, 1873; Item No. 118; 7 sheets (Box 5)
    - Pacific Coast Fourth Reader, 1875; Item No. 118; 7 sheets (Box 5)
    - Pacific Coast Fourth Reader, 1878; Item No. 118; 2 sheets; 5 copies of 4th Reader (Box 5)
    - What Montana Educators say about Bancroft Readers, Item No. 118 (Box 5)
    - Pacific Coast Second Reader, Item No. 118; 5 sheets (Box 5)
    - Sargent's Standard Series of Speakers Intermediate Speaker, 1858; Item No. 118; 3 Sheets (Box 5)
      (Peggy Christian's copy)
    - Pacific Coast Series Fifth Reader, 1873; Item No. 118; 8 sheets (Box 5)
    - Pacific Coast Series Fifth Reader, 1878; Item No. 118; 6 sheets (Box 5)
    - Silver Carols for Day Schools, Item No. 118; 4 sheets (Box 5)
    - The Adoption of Pacific Coast Readers, Item No. 118; 10 sheets (Box 5)
    - The Adoption of Pacific Coast Readers, Item No. 118; 3 sheets (Box 5)
    - CSLU and Oregon State Library, Item No. 118 (Box 5)
      "Can't make comparison as haven't the same pages."
    - What Montana Educations say of Bancroft's Readers, Item No. 118; 8 pages (Box 5)
    - Sargents Standard Series of Speakers No. 2 by Epes Sargent, Item No. 118; 3 sheets (Box 5)
      Peggy Christian has only copy known.
  - Some H.H. Bancroft publications, Item No. 119 (Box 6)
    Items not on checklist:
    Bancroft Library tickets of admission
    Bancroft Co. stationery
    Evolution of a Library (1901)
    Miscellaneous articles and ephemera re Hubert Howe Bancroft.
    - Mabel Vaughan (CSL ) only copy known, Item No. 119; 2 sheets (Box 6)
    - H.H. Bancroft & Co.'s Law Catalogue, Messrs Little; Brown & Co.'s Miscellaneous books, Item No. 119; 4 pages. (Box 6)
      (RFA has original only copy known?)
    - H.H. Bancroft & Company's Law Catalogue, 1865; Item No. 119; 1 page (Box 6)
    - Mexico, Item No. 119; 19 pages (Box 6)
    - "The Hermitage" and other poems, Item No. 119; 1 page (Box 6)
    - Mexico, Item No. 119; 19 pages (Box 6)
    - The Great Metropolis, Item No. 119; 1 page (Box 6)
    - Bancroft's Catalogue of Subscription Works, 1866; Item No. 119; 1 page (Box 6)
    - Mexico and the United States, Item No. 119; 33 pages (Box 6)
  - Miscellaneous H.H. Bancroft and A.L.B.
    - Minutes of the California Annual Conference--Methodist Episcopal Church, 1867; Item No. 120; 2 pages (Box 6)
    - Attention Pacific Encyclopedist, March 13, 1872; Item No. 120; 2 sheets (Box 6)
      "(I have original)"
    - The New California Reports, Charles H. Parker, Esq., 1869; Item No. 120; 1 sheet (Box 6)
    - H.H. Bancroft & Company's Law Catalogue, 1865; Item No. 120; 1 page (Box 6)
    - This Day Published, 1861; Item No. 120; 4 pages (Box 6)
    - History of the Great Rebellion, Item No. 120; 1 page (Box 6)
    - The Bookseller H.H. Bancroft, 1858; Item No. 120; 1 page (Box 6)
    - The Value of Hydrocarbon Oils, A.L.B. and Co., 1870; Item No. 120; 1 page proofs (Box 6)
    - Historical Works of Hubert Howe Bancroft, May 7, 1886; Item No. 121; 1 page (Box 6)
    - Quarterly Book List Bancroft Company, January 1888; Item No. 121; 1 page (Box 6)
    - Bancroft Library for sale, Item No. 121; 4 pages, duplicates (Box 6)
    - Maps and Guides for sale, 1877; Item No. 121; 1 page (Box 6)
    - Bancroft's Christmas Messenger, Item No. 121; 4 pages (Box 6)
    - H.H. Bancroft's & Company Bookseller & Stationers, 1868; Item No. 121; 1 page (Box 6)
    - A.L. Bancroft & Co. Map Publishing, Item No. 121; 1 page (Box 6)
    - Publishers Notice, Item No. 121; 1 page (Box 6)
    - Order of Publication, Item No. 121; 1 page (Box 6)
    - The Bancroft Historical Library, Item No. 122; 36 pages (Box 6)
    - Letter of U.S. Attorney on value of Library, Item No. 122; 2 pages. (Box 6)
    - A brief account of the literary undertakings of H.H.Bancroft, Item No. 122; 12 sheets (Box 6)
    - "The Complete Parallel Bible at CLU but I have not seen", Item No. 123; 1 sheet (Box 6)
    - A.L. Bancroft & Co., Item No. 123; 1 page (Box 6)
    - [?]., 1887; Item No. 123; 1 page (Box 6)
    - Reports of Cases Matthew P. Deady TP, 1872; Item No. 123; 1 page (Box 6)
    - Letter, HHB (holograph) to R.E. Cowan in praise of 1914 Bib., Item No. 123; 1 page (Box 6)
      "I do not have the original."
    - West American History Autograph edition with HHB autograph, Item No. 123; (original? proof sheet?); 1 page (Box 6)
  - Fullerton Special Collections (Stone papers), Item No. 124 (Box 6)
    - Azariah Bancroft (HHB and ALB father) journal, Item No. 124; 5 pages (Box 6)
    - My notes on newsprint, Item No. 124; 5 pages (Box 6)
    - Stone's resignation, Item No. 124; 11 pages (Box 6)
    - Stone's business correspondence with Bancroft, Item No. 124; 7 pages (Box 6)
    - Newspaper article vindicating Stone, Item No. 124; 1 page (Box 6)
  - Not Bancroft but related to, Item No. 125 (Box 6)
    - Cinco de Mayo, Item No. 125; 21 sheets (Box 6)
    - History of the Bench and Bar Shuck Law Reference, Item No. 125; 5 pages (Box 6)
    - Reports of Cases determined in the District Courts, Vol.1 Boalt Hall not Bancroft, 1858; Item No. 125; 2 pages (Box 6)
    - Reports of Cases determined in the District Courts, Vol.1, CSL not Bancroft, 1858; Item No. 125; 2 pages (Box 6)
    - Reports of Cases determined in the District Courts, Vol.1 Number 5, Boalt Hall not Bancroft, 1858; Item No. 125; 2 pages (Box 6)
    - Reports of Cases Vol.II. No.2, Boalt Hall not Bancroft, 1858; Item No. 125; 2 pages (Box 6)
    - Reports of Cases Vol.II, CSL, no title, no preface not Bancroft, Item No. 125; 1 page (Box 6)
    - Reports of Cases No.3, Boalt Hall not Bancroft, 1858; Item No. 125; 2 pages (Box 6)
    - The History Company Deportamento Editorial Español Carta Circular, Item No. 125; 1 page (Box 6)
    - Orden de Publicacion Obras Literarias de Huberto Howe Bancroft superimposed on page of Library Material, Item No. 125; 1 page, proof sheet? (Box 6)
    - Special Offer We Pay Freights Books Manufactored and Shipped from St.Louis, Mo. ....The History Company, Publishers. History Building 721 Market St. San Francisco, California, Item No. 125; 1 page (Box 6)
    - Sitka, Alaska, letter to HHB from Alaska Historica Society, March 25, 1890; Item No. 125; 1 page (Box 6)
    - The Western Shore Gazetteer and Commercial Directory, Item No. 125; 1 page (Box 6)
  - About Bancroft, Item No. 126 (Box 6)
    - The Paper World, March 1881; Item No. 126; 6 pages (Box 6)
      covering letter from George L. Harding, June 12, 1950
    - Bancroft's Exhaustive Work Described by Collaborator (Los Angeles Times), March 10, 1918; Item No. 126; 2 pages (Box 6)
    - San Diego History News: Bancroft Park a Reality, February 1978; Item No. 126; clipping (Box 6)
    - (1 port) UCLA Folder, Item No. 126; 2 pages (Box 6)
    - World Life or Comparative Geology, Item No. 126; 2 pages (Box 6)
      With the respects of A.L. Bancroft & Company (pink slip tipped in) not Bancroft, UCLA
    - The Panama Canal: San Francisco Exposition, San Diego Exposition, The Bancroft Co., 1915; Item No. 126; 31 pages, 15.5 x 8.8 cm (Box 6)
- 3 x 5 cards
  "Preserve carefully--many of these Have H.R.Wagner's original notes."
  - H.H. Bancroft & Co., 1857-May-1870; Item No. 127; 2 ½ inches (Box 7)
  - A.L. Bancroft & Co., 1870-1886; Item No. 127; 3 ¼ inches (Box 7)
  - The History Company, 1886-1905; Item No. 127; 1 ½ inches (Box 7)
  - HHB ALB Maps, etc., unlocated, Item No. 127; 3 ½ inches (Box 7)
    "Doubt unlocated, many since found."
  - More ALB cards, Item No. 127; 3 inches (Box 7)
    "unlocated but many since found with notes"
  - New L.L. Bancroft Co., later, after 1886; Item No. 127; 1 inch (Box 7)
  - The Bancroft Co., 1887 to 1905; Item No. 127; ½ inch, Miscellanous 2 ½ inches (Box 7)
  - W.B. Bancroft, Item No. 127; 7 cards (Box 7)
    - Sold but not published by A.L. Bancroft & Co., 1882; Item No. 127; 14 cards (Box 7)